<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ECE InfoKiosk</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="faculty_prompt">Faculty</string>
    <string name="map_prompt">Map</string>
    <string name="clubs_prompt">Orgs</string>
    <string name="clubs_full">Organizations</string>
    <string name="events_prompt">Events</string>
    <string name="games_prompt">Games</string>
    <string name="info_prompt">Info</string>
    <string name="height_prompt">Tap Here to Lower Controls</string>
    <string name="greeting_prompt">Welcome to the ECE Kiosk!</string>
    <string name="departments">Select a Department</string>
    <string name="chemical">Chemical &amp; &#xD;Biomedical</string>
    <string name="electrical">Electrical &amp; &#xD;Computer</string>
    <string name="mechanical">Mechanical</string>
    <string name="industrial">Industrial &amp; &#xD;Manufacturing</string>
    <string name="civil">Civil &amp; &#xD;Environmental</string>
    <string name="back_prompt">Back</string>
    <string name="title_activity_chem">Chem</string>
    <string name="build_1">First Floor</string>
    <string name="build_2">Second Floor</string>
    <string name="build_3">Third Floor</string>
    <string name="info_title">College Information</string>\
    <string name="info_text">Put info text here</string>

    //Games stuff
    <string name="correct_prompt">Correct!</string>
    <string name="incorrect_prompt">Incorrect!</string>
    <string name="next_prompt">Next Question</string>
    <string name="trivia_title">Trivia Game</string>
    <string name="quest_1">What year was the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering established? </string>
    <string name="q1a">1983</string>
    <string name="q1b">1851</string>
    <string name="q1c">1954</string>
    <string name="q1d">1997</string>

    <string name="quest_2">This professor was elected to the National Academy of Inventors, a feat that only 581 other people world wide have accomplished.</string>
    <string name="q2a">Dr. Rodney Roberts</string>
    <string name="q2b">Dr. Ming Yu</string>
    <string name="q2c">Dr. Jianping Zheng</string>
    <string name="q2d">Dr. Uwe Meyer-Baese</string>

    <string name="quest_3">How many credit hours does an ECE major need to graduate?</string>
    <string name="q3a">120</string>
    <string name="q3b">124</string>
    <string name="q3c">128</string>
    <string name="q3d">132</string>

    <string name="quest_4">Which of these ECE professors completed all of their schooling at the FSU-FAMU College of Engineering?</string>
    <string name="q4a">Dr. Walid Hadi</string>
    <string name="q4b">Dr. Jerris Hooker</string>
    <string name="q4c">Dr. Hui Li</string>
    <string name="q4d">Dr. Reginald Perry</string>

    //Chem faculty
    <string name="alamo">Rufina Alamo, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="chella">Ravidran Chella, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="chung">Hoyong Chung, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="finney">Wright Finney, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="grant">Samuel Grant, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="guan">Jingjiao Guan, Ph.D.</string>
    //continue

    //Elec faculty
    <string name="andrei">Petru Andrei, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="arghandeh">Reza Arghandeh, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="arora">Rajendra K. Arora, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="barnes">Jerome Barnes</string>
    <string name="bernadin">Shonda Bernadin, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="brooks">Geoffrey Brooks, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="harvey">Bruce A. Harvey, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="ldebrunner">Linda S. DeBrunner, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="vdebrunner">Victor DeBrunner, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="edrington">Chris S. Edrington, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="faruque">Omar Faruque, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="foo">Simon Y. Foo, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="hadi">Walid A. Hadi, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="islam">Md. Shafiul Islam, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="hooker">Jerris Hooker, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="kwan">Bing W. Kwan, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="li">Hui Li, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="lipo">Thomas Lipo, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="mcginnis">Roger D. McGinnis, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="meyer">Uwe H. Meyer-Baese, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="moss">Pedro Moss, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="pamidi">Sastry V. Pamidi, Ph.D., MBA</string>
    <string name="perry">Reginald J. Perry, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="roberts">Rodney Roberts, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="steurer">Michael Steurer, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="tung">Leonard J. Tung, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="weatherspoon">Mark H. Weatherspoon, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="yu">Ming Yu, Ph.D.</string>
    <string name="zheng">Jim P. Zheng, Ph.D.</string>
    //end Elec faculty


    //biographies
    <string name="andrei_bio">
        Office: AME Building 213\n
        (850) 410-6589\n
        (850) 645-0137\n
        pandrei@eng.famu.fsu.edu\n
        Education\n
        \tPh.D., ECE, University of Maryland, College Park, 2004\n
        \tM.S., Physics, Al. I. Cuza University, Romania, 1999\n
        \tB.S., Physics, Al. I. Cuza University, Romania, 1997\n
        Research Interests\n
        \tMagnetics\n
        \tElectrochemical systems\n
        \tNano and power electronic devices\n
        \tNoise and hysteresis\n\n
        Petru Andrei received his Ph.D. in Electrical and Computer Engineering from the University of Maryland, College Park in 2004 and his M.S. and B.S. in Physics from the Alexandru I. Cuza University in Romania. He joined the FAMU-FSU College of Engineering in Fall 2004.\n
        Dr. Andrei is working on the modeling and simulation of nanoscale and power semiconductor devices, energy storage devices, magnetic materials, and on computational electromagnetics. He is particularly interested in the modeling of metal-air and Li-ion batteries, supercapacitors, fuel cells, analysis of fluctuations, variability, and noise in electronic devices, quantum induced effects in nanoscale devices, redesign and optimization techniques, inverse problems, modeling and analysis of the magnetic properties of nanostructure systems, fast multipole methods, hysteresis, and thermal relaxation phenomena in nanostructures.\n
        Dr. Andrei is a member of the Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers (IEEE) and American Physical Society (APS) and is currently serving as referee for numerous journals.
    </string>

    <string name="harvey_bio">
        Office: A344\n
        (850) 410-6451\n
        bharvey@fsu.edu\n
        Education\n
        \tPh.D., Electrical Engineering, Georgia Institute of Technology, 1991\n
        \tM.S., Electrical Engineering, University of Alabama in Huntsville, 1987\n
        \tB.E.E., Auburn University, 1984\n
        Research Interests\n
        \tWireless Communication and Networks\n
        \tSpread-spectrum communications\n
        \tReal-time DSP in communication systems\n
        \tRemote data collection and lightning surge suppression/protection\n\n
        Dr. Bruce Harvey (S\'81–M\'84–S\'88–M\'91–SM\'98) was born in Stoughton, Massachusetts, USA on December 20, 1961. He received the B.E.E. (Co-op, Highest Honor) from Auburn University in 1984. He received the M.S.E.E. from the University of Alabama in Huntsville in 1987 and the Ph.D. in Electrical Engineering from Georgia Institute of Technology in 1991 specializing in communications theory and error control coding.\n
        In September 1997 he joined the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering at the FAMU-FSU Joint College of Engineering in Tallahassee, Florida, and currently holds the rank of Associate Professor. Dr. Harvey was the Associate Chair of the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering from 2004-2010, and is once again serving in this capacity (since 2013). He was a Research Engineer I at the Georgia Tech Research Institute (GTRI) from 1984-1986 and a Lead Engineer at Phase IV Systems, Inc. from 1986-1988. From 1991-1997 he was a Research Engineer II and then Senior Research Engineer in the Communications Division of GTRI.\n
        His current fields of interest include wireless communication, error control coding, telecommunication systems, and spread-spectrum communications.\n
    </string>

    <string name="hooker_bio">
        Office: A342\n
        (850) 410-6463\n
        jh09c@my.fsu.edu\n
        Education\n
        \tPh.D., Florida A&amp;M University, Tallahassee, 2010\n
        \tM.S., Florida A&amp;M University, Tallahassee, 2006\n
        \tB.E.E.,Florida State University, Tallahassee, 2002\n
        Research Interests\n
        \tSpiral coil resonators\n
        \tHTS thin-film resonators\n
        Current Research Projects\n
        \tDevelopment of HTS technology for use in NMR probes\n
        Jerris Hooker received his Ph.D., and M.S. in Electrical and Computer Engineering from Florida A&amp;M University in 2010 and 2006 respectively. His B.S. in Electrical and Computer Engineering was obtained from Florida State University in 2002. Dr. Hooker is currently a postdoctoral researcher at the National High Magnetic Field Laboratory and an adjunct professor of Electrical and Computer Engineering Department, FAMU-FSU college of Engineering. His research interest include modelling of resonant devices, HTS NMR probes, spiral resonators, and numerical methods. Dr. Hooker also serves as a mentor for the SAIL High School Robotics Club, assisting in the design, construction, and optimization of robots for the FIRST Robotics competition as well as other projects.\n
    </string>


    <string name="foo_bio">
        Office: A341\n
        (850) 410-6474\n
        (850) 410-6622\n
        sfoo@fsu.edu\n
        simon.foo@famu.edu\n

        Education/n
        \tPh.D., Electrical and Computer Engineering, University of South Carolina, 1988\n
        \tM.S., Electrical and Computer Engineering, University of South Carolina, 1985\n
        \tB.S., Electrical Engineering, University of South Carolina, 1983\n
        Research Interests\n
        \tComputational Intelligence\n
        \tReconfigurable Antennas\n
        \tModeling of Electro-Mechanical Actuator (EMA)\n
        \tElectromagnetic interference (EMI) filtering\n
        \tRegenerative electric power\n
        \tMore Electric Aircraft (MEA)\n
        \tMulti-junction Photovoltaics\n
        Dr. Foo is a tenured Professor at the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering at Florida A&amp;M University and Florida State University. His research contributions have been in the areas of computational intelligence, random number generators, field programmable gate array (FPGA) applications, and photovoltaics. Dr. Foo has authored or co-authored over 100 refereed technical papers and contributed to two book chapters. He has also graduated more than 30 MS and PhD students. He is the Principal Investigator of at least 20 funded research projects with total funding of over 3 million dollars. His primary research sponsors include the National Security Agency, National Science Foundation, U. S. Air Force, Boeing Aircraft Company, and the Florida Department of Transportation. He also serves as a technical advisor to Airbus in the area of fire detection in aircraft cargo bays. Dr. Foo is a member of Eta Kappa Nu Electrical Engineering Honor Society (since 1982).
    </string>
</resources>
